{
    "subject": "resource/Dinteloord",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/North_Brabant",
    "human_readable": "Dinteloord is part of North Brabant.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7108412981033325,
            "question": "Where is Dinteloord located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5429760813713074,
            "question": "What province is Dinteloord part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251303315162659,
            "question": "To what geographical area does Dinteloord belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45961862802505493,
            "question": "Is Dinteloord a city or part of a larger province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44240522384643555,
            "question": "Dinteloord is part of what administrative unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39377492666244507,
            "question": "Within which Dutch region would you find Dinteloord?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36473095417022705,
            "question": "Can you tell me the administrative division to which Dinteloord belongs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32589292526245117,
            "question": "In which region of the Netherlands is Dinteloord situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24582186341285706,
            "question": "What is the name of the Dutch province that includes Dinteloord?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19671353697776794,
            "question": "What is the larger political entity encompassing Dinteloord?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dinteloord is part of North Brabant.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2684_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the Dutch province that includes Dinteloord?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2684_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which region of the Netherlands is Dinteloord situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2684_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the administrative division to which Dinteloord belongs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2684_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2684_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Dinteloord being located in the Noord-Brabant region of Netherlands, and another document lists North Brabant as the location where Dinteloord is situated. This supports the triple that Dinteloord is part of North Brabant."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Dinteloord is located in the province of North Brabant, Netherlands. Therefore, the statement \"Dinteloord is part of North Brabant\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}